



Education

2015-08 -2017-12 Ohio State University

B.A in Journalism, Minor in International Relations & Foreign Diplomacy GPA: 3.2

2014-08 -2015-05 Colby College

Majored in Biochemistry GPA:3.4 Transfered



Experience

2015 -2017 Freelance Writer (Mandarin)

College Daily

- Responsible for interviewing news subjects involved in current events that triggers an interest for general college students
- Actively Involved in more than 20 stories
- Able to obtain a high volume of digital traffic, an average of 50,000 clicks each article.

2015-11 -2016-12

Customer Service

Wexner Medical Center

- · Actively interacted with customers for satisfactory services
- · Worked in a team to solve customers' concerns
- Trained new employees

2016-09 present

Retail Seller

Self-Starter

- Created my own small business
- Advertising my products through popular Chinese social medias(can be tracked)
- Sold less than \$3,000 in my spare time outside schooling (record can be tracked)



Additional Experience

2017-06 -2017-08

Brandt-Roberts Galleries

Marketing Intern

- Assisted with the editorials, press releases and newsletter
- Composed digital show invitations to the gallery clients and artists
- Responsible for managing social media posting on Facebook and Instagram

2016-09 -2017-05

Writer (English)

Lantern

- Wrote 13 stories in English
- Self-produced multimedia content

Ø

Professional References

Michelle Brandt, Brandt-Roberts Galleries, Business Owner

642 N. High Street. Columbus. Ohio, 43215

Phone: 614 - 223- 1655

E-mail: info@brandtrobertsgalleries.com Relationship: Internship Supervisor

Spencer Hunt, Director of The Lantern, Ohio State University

271 Journalism Building, 242 W 18th Avenue

614-247-7030

Email: hunt.754@osu.edu

Relationship: Lantern Media Director

Personal Info

Address

571 Stinchcomb Drive. Columbus, Ohio. 43202

Phone

(207)-313-0672

E-mail

yutingyangosu@gmail.com



Summary

A recent OSU graduate with 2 years experiences communication management in Mandarin and English, motivated and detail-oriented, proficient at negotiating with people across cultures and languages as well as working under intensive deadlines, seeking to contribute my communication skills to your team.



Communication

Advanced

Writing Skills



Microsoft





English - Certified



Native level (written article published)

Mandarin-Certified



Native level (hit writer in popular social media channels)

Japanese

